Welcome to Gulim. Click "Start" and proceed with Google Sign-In to authenticate.
Select the Google account. This account's spreadsheet will be used as the database.
Since the app is currently unverified, click "Advanced" and "Go to gulim.co.kr" to bypass the warning.
[Crucial] The app requests spreadsheets scope. This is required to read/write specific cell data using the Google Sheets API.
On the welcome screen, use the Google Drive Picker to select the specific investment spreadsheet to link.
[Read Operation] The dashboard uses sheets.values.get to read specific cell ranges (assets, returns) from the user's sheet.
[Write Operation] Moving to the History tab to demonstrate writing data. We will add a new dividend record.
Enter stock info and amount. When "Save" is clicked, the app prepares a sheets.values.append request.
[Verification] The new row is successfully appended to the specific sheet. This granular cell-level update requires the spreadsheets scope.
In Settings, users can change the linked file ID. The app only accesses the specific spreadsheet selected here.