Welcome to Gullim — "Investment records become lifelong assets." Click "Start" and select "Continue with Google" to sign in.
Select your Google account. A warning appears because the app is pending verification. Click "Advanced" then "Go to gulim.co.kr" to proceed.
Gullim requests access to Google Drive and Google Sheets. These permissions allow the app to read and write your investment data. Check the boxes and click "Continue" to grant access.
Welcome screen appears. Click "Select from Google Drive" to connect your spreadsheet. Use the file picker to search and select your investment record sheet.
Dashboard loads with data pulled directly from your Google Sheet. View total assets (33.7M KRW), profit/loss, and daily balance trend graph.
Navigate to the "History" tab. View monthly transaction summaries including dividends, deposits, and withdrawals — all synced from your spreadsheet.
Add a new record manually. Click the pencil icon, select "Manual Input," enter date (2025.12.15), stock name, and dividend amount (100,000 KRW).
Save the entry. "Dividend history saved" confirms success. This data is written directly to your Google Spreadsheet in real-time.
Switch to the "Portfolio" tab. View your holdings, current valuations, return rates, and portfolio weights — all fetched from your spreadsheet.
Go to "Settings" and select "Sheet Connection Management" to change the linked spreadsheet.
Select "Change to another sheet," paste a new Google Sheet URL, and click "Change." You control which file Gullim can access.
Dashboard reloads with the new sheet data. Total assets now show 60.9M KRW with +128.2% return. All your data stays in YOUR Google Drive.